Painting Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting France (Box 45)
  - Gothic (Box 46)
    - LANCRET, Nicolas, 1690-1749 (Box 80)
      - Paintings (Box 80)
        - Berlin (Box 80)
        - Leningrad (Box 80)
        - New York (Box 80)
        - Paris (Box 80)
        - Washington (Box 80)
    - LARGILLIERE, Nicholas de, 1656-1746 (Box 80)
      - London (Box 80)
      - Paris (Box 80)
    - LA TOUR, Georges, 1593-1652 (Box 80)
      - Berlin (Box 80)
      - Epinal (Box 80)
      - Grenoble (Box 80)
      - Munich (Box 80)
      - Nantes (Box 80)
      - Paris (Box 80)
      - Rennes (Box 80)
    - LA TOUR, M. Quentin de, 1704-1788 (Box 80)
      - Paris (Box 80)
      - S. Quentin (Box 80)
    - LAURENCIN, Marie, 1885-1956 (Box 80)
    - LAURENS, Henri, 1885-1954 (Box 80)
    - LAURENS, Jean Paul, 1836-1922 (Box 81)
    - LAURENT, Ernest, 1859-1929 (Box 81)
    - LE BRUN, Charles, 1619-1690 (Box 81)
      - Drawings (Box 81)
      - Paintings (Box 81)
        - Florence (Box 81)
        - Paris (Box 81)
        - Vaux-le-Vicomte (Box 81)
        - Versailles (Box 81)
    - LE CLERG, Jean, 1585-1633 (Box 81)
    - LE CORBUSIER, 1887-1965 (Box 81)
    - LE FAUCONNIER, Henri (Box 81)
    - LE FEBVRE, Jules, ca. 1835-1912 (Box 81)
    - LEGER, Fernand, 1881-1955 (Box 81)
      - Cities, Museums, Galleries (Box 81)
      - Brussels (Box 82)
      - Chicago (Box 82)
      - Lausanne (Box 82)
      - New Haven (Box 82)
      - New York (Box 82)
      - Paris (Box 82)
      - Philadelphia (Box 82)
      - Venice (Box 82)
    - LEJEUNE, Louis Francois, 1775-1848 (Box 82)
    - LEMAIRE, Jean, 1597-1659 (Box 82)
    - LE MOYNE, Francois, 1688-1737 (Box 82)
    - LE NAIN, the brothers (Box 82)
    - LE NAIN, Antoine, 1588-1648 (Box 82)
    - LE NAIN, Louis, ca. 1593-1648 (Box 82)
      - Hartford (Box 82)
      - Paris (Box 82)
    - LE NAIN, Mathieu, 1607?-1677 (Box 82)
    - LEPICIE, Michie, 1735-1785 (Box 82)
    - LEROLLE, Henri, 1848-1929 (Box 82)
    - LE SUEUR, Eusatce, 1617-1655 (Box 83)
      - Le Mans (Box 83)
      - Paris (Box 83)
    - LEVY, Emile (Box 83)
    - LHERMITTE, Leon Augustin, 1844-1925 (Box 83)
    - LHOTE, Andre, 1885-1934 (Box 83)
    - Master of Saint Sebastian, d. ca. 1508 (LIEFERINCX, Josse) (Box 83)
    - LIPCCHITZ, J., 1891- (Box 83)
    - LOO, Amedee van, ca. 1719-1795 (Box 83)
    - LOO, Charles Andre van, 1705-1765 (Box 83)
    - LOO, Jean-Baptiste van, 1684-1745 (Box 83)
    - LOO, Jules Cesar van, 1743-1821 (Box 83)
    - LOO, Louis Michel van (Box 83)
    - LORRAINE, Claude, 1600-1682 (Box 83)
    - LOUTHERBOURG, Philip James de, 1740-1812 (Box 83)
    - LUCE, Maximilien, 1858-1941 (Box 83)
    - LURCAT, Jean, 1892- (Box 83)
    - MAGRITTE, Rene, 1898-1967 (Box 83)
    - MAIGNAN, Albert P.R., 1845-1908 (Box 83)
    - MAILLOL, Aristide, 1861-1944 (Box 83)
    - MALOUEL, Jean (Box 83)
    - MANESSIER, Alfred (Box 83)
    - MANET, Edouard, 1832-1883 (Box 83)
      - Cartoons and Comparisons (Box 83–84)
      - Drawings (Box 84)
      - Paintings (Box 84)
        - Berlin (Box 84)
        - Boston (Box 84)
        - Budapest (Box 84)
        - Chicago (Box 84)
        - Mannheim (Box 84–85)
        - New York (Box 85)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 85)
        - Paris (Box 85)
          - Louvre (Box 85)
        - Philadelphia (Box 85)
        - Tournai (Box 85)
        - Upperville, VA (Box 85)
        - Washington (Box 85)
    - MARCHAND, Andre, 1877- (Box 85)
    - MARILHAT, Prosper, G.A., 1811-1847 (Box 85)
    - MARMION, Simon, ca. 1425-1489 (Box 85)
    - MARQUET, Albert, 1875-1947 (Box 85)
    - MASSON, Andre, 1896-1987 (Box 85)
      - Bern (Box 85)
      - Buffalo (Box 85)
      - New York (Box 85)
      - Paris (Box 85)
    - MATHIOLZ, Christine M. (Box 85)
    - MATISSE, Henri, 1869-1954 (Box 85)
      - Drawings (Box 85–86)
      - Paintings (Box 86)
        - Baltimore (Box 86)
        - Buffalo (Box 86)
        - Chicago (Box 86)
        - Cleveland (Box 86)
        - Copenhagen (Box 86)
        - Grenoble (Box 86)
        - Leningrad (Box 86)
        - Merion, PA (Box 86)
        - Moscow (Box 86)
        - New York (Box 86)
        - Paris (Box 86)
    - MAYER, Marie Francois Constance, 1775-1821 (Box 86)
    - MEISSONIER, J. L.F., 1815-1891 (Box 86)
      - Drawings (Box 86)
      - Paintings (Box 86–87)
        - London (Box 87)
        - New York (Box 87)
        - Paris (Box 87)
          - Louvre (Box 87)
    - MELLAN, Claude, 1598-1688 (Box 87)
    - MERCIER, Philippe, 1689-1760 (Box 87)
    - MERYON, Charles, 1821-1868 (Box 87)
    - METZINGER, Jean, 1883-1956 (Box 87)
    - MEUSNIER, Philippe, 1655-1734 (Box 87)
    - MICHEL, Georges, 1763-1843 (Box 87)
    - MIGNARD, Pierre, I, 1612-1695 (Box 87)
    - MILLET, Francisque, II, 1666-1713 (Box 87)
    - MILLET, Jean Francois, 1814-1875 (Box 87)
      - Photographs (Box 87)
      - Drawings (Box 87)
        - Studies for the Gleaners (Box 88)
        - Study for the Goose Girl (Box 88)
        - Studies for the Sower (Box 88)
      - Paintings (Box 88)
        - Boston (Box 88)
        - Chicago (Box 88)
        - London (Box 88)
        - Marseilles (Box 88)
        - New York (Box 88)
        - Paris (Box 88)
          - Louvre (Box 88)
    - MIRAILIET, Jean, 1394-1457 (Box 88)
    - MONET, Claude, 1840-1926 (Box 88–89)
      - Photographs (Box 89)
      - Known Cities (Box 89)
      - Berlin (Box 89)
      - Boston (Box 89)
      - Cambridge (Box 89)
      - Chicago (Box 89)
      - Detroit (Box 89)
      - Farmington (Box 89)
      - Leningrad (Box 89)
      - London (Box 89)
      - New York (Box 89)
      - Paris (Box 89)
        - Louvre (Box 89–90)
        - Luxembourg (Box 90)
      - Vienna (Box 90)
      - Washington (Box 90)
      - Williamstown (Box 90)
      - Zurich (Box 90)
    - MONTICELLI, Adolphe, 1824-1880 (Box 90)
    - MOREAU, Gustave, 1826-1898 (Box 90)
    - MOREAU, Louis Gabriel, the elder (Box 90)
    - MOREAU, Jean-Michel, le jeune, 1741-1814 (Box 90)
    - MORISOT, Berthe, 1841-1895 (Box 90)
    - MOROT, Amie, 1850-1913 (Box 90)
    - MUENIER, Jules A., 1863- (Box 90)
    - NANTEUIL, Robert (Box 90)
    - NATOIRE, Charles Joseph, 1700-1777 (Box 90)
    - NATTIER, Jean Marc, 1685-1766 (Box 90)
      - New York (Box 90)
      - Paris (Box 90)
    - NEUVILLE, Alphonse M. de., 1835-1885 (Box 90)
    - NICOLLE, Victor, 1754-1826 (Box 90)
    - OCTAVIEN, Francois (Box 90)
    - OLLIVIER, Michel, 1712-1784 (Box 90)
    - OUDRY, Jean Baptiste, 1686-1755 (Box 90)
    - OZENFANT, Amedee (Box 90)
    - PAGAVA, Vera (Box 91)
    - PAJOU, Augustin, 1730-1809 (Box 91)
    - PARROCEL, Joseph, 1646-1704 (Box 91)
    - PATEL, Antoine, 1648-1707 (Box 91)
    - PATEL, Pierre (Box 91)
    - PATER, Jean Baptiste Joseph, 1695-1736 (Box 91)
      - London (Box 91)
      - New York (Box 91)
    - PELEZ, Ferrand E. (Box 91)
    - PERREAL, Jean (Box 91)
    - PERRET, Aime, 1847-1927 (Box 91)
    - PERRIER, Francois, 1590-1650 (Box 91)
    - PERRONNEAU, Jean Baptiste, 1715-1783 (Box 91)
      - Paris (Box 91)
    - PETTIJEAN, Hippolyte, 1854-1929 (Box 91)
    - PEYRON, J.-F. P., 1744-1814 (Box 91)
    - PEYRONNET, Dominique-Paul (Box 91)
    - PICABIA, Francis, 1879-1953 (Box 91)
    - PICASSO, Pablo, 1881-1973 (Box 91)
    - PICHARD, Janie (Box 91)
    - PIETTE, Ludovic, 1826-1877 (Box 91)
    - PIGNON, Edouard, 1905- (Box 91)
    - PINEAU, Nicolas, 1684-1754 (Box 91)
    - PISSARRO, Camille, 1831-1903 (Box 91–92)
      - Paris (Box 92)
      - Washington (Box 92)
    - PISSARRO, Lucien (Box 92)
    - PORTAIL, Jacque Andre, 1695-1759 (Box 92)
    - POUSSIN, Nicolas, 1594-1665 (Box 92)
      - Drawings (Box 92)
      - Paintings (Box 92–93)
        - Berlin (Box 93)
        - Chantilly (Box 93)
        - Chatsworth (Box 93)
        - Chicago (Box 93)
        - Dresden (Box 93)
        - Leningrad (Box 93)
        - London (Box 93)
          - Collection of Earl of Ellesaere (Box 93)
          - National Gallery (Box 93)
        - Madrid (Box 93)
        - New York (Box 93)
        - Paris (Box 93)
          - Louvre (Box 93–94)
            - Eleazer and Rebecca (Box 94)
            - Et in Arcadiaego (Box 94)
              - Four Seasons (Winter, Summer, Spring, Autumn) (Box 94)
              - Philistines Struck by Plague (Box 94)
              - Rape of the Sabines (Box 94)
              - S. James Major (Box 94)
        - Philadelphia (Box 94)
        - Rome (Box 94)
        - Washington (Box 94)
    - PRIEUR, J.L., 1759-1795 (Box 94)
    - PRINET, Rene, 1861- (Box 94)
    - PRUD'HON, Pierre-Paul, 1758-1823 (Box 94)
      - Drawings (Box 94)
      - Paintings (Box 94)
        - Paris (Box 94)
    - PUGET, Pierre, 1620-1694 (Box 94)
    - PUVIS de Chavannes, 1824-1898 (Box 94–95)
      - Amiens (Box 95)
      - Boston (Box 95)
      - Chartres (Box 95)
      - Lyon (Box 95)
      - Paris (Box 95)
      - Washington (Box 95)
    - RAFFAELI, J.F., 1850-1924 (Box 95)
    - RAFFET, Denis Augusute Marie, 1804-1860 (Box 95)
    - RANSON, Paul (Box 95)
    - REDON, Odilon, 1840-1916 (Box 95)
      - Cleveland (Box 95)
      - New York (Box 95)
      - Paris (Box 95)
      - Washington (Box 95)
      - Winterthur (Box 95)
    - REGNAULT, Henri-Victor, 1810-1878 (Box 95)
    - REGNAULT, Jean Baptiste, 1754-1829 (Box 95)
    - REGNIER, Nicholas, 1590-1667 (Box 95)
    - RENOIR, Pierre Auguste, 1841-1919 (Box 95)
      - Drawings (Box 95)
      - Paintings (Box 95–96)
        - Private Collection (Box 96)
        - Places (Box 96)
        - Chicago (Box 96)
        - Cleveland (Box 96)
        - Essen (Box 96)
        - Frankfurt (Box 96)
        - Germantown, PA (Box 96)
        - London (Box 96)
        - New York (Box 96)
        - Paris (Box 96)
          - Louvre (Box 96–97)
          - Luxembourg (Box 97)
        - Philadelphia (Box 97)
        - Providence (Box 97)
        - Stockholm (Box 97)
        - Washington (Box 97)
        - Williamstown (Box 97)
    - RESTOUT, Jean, 1692-1768 (Box 97)
    - RIBEMONT, Dessaignes Georges (Box 97)
    - RIGAUD, Hyacinth, 1659-1743 (Box 97)
      - Aix (Box 97)
      - Paris (Box 97)
      - Vienna (Box 97)
    - ROBERT, Hubert, 1733-1808 (Box 97)
      - New York (Box 97)
      - Paris (Box 97)
      - Worcester (Box 97)
    - ROBERT, Leopold, 1794-1833 (Box 97)
    - ROCHER, Maurice (Box 97)
    - RODIN, Auguste, 1840-1917 (Box 97–98)
      - New York (Box 98)
    - ROLL, Alfred Philippe, 1847-1919 (Box 98)
    - ROUAULT, George, 1871-1958 (Box 98)
      - Unknown Collection (Box 98)
      - Private Collection (Box 98)
      - Places (Box 98)
      - Cleveland (Box 98)
      - New York (Box 98)
    - ROUSSEAU, Henri, 1844-1910 (Box 98)
      - New York (Box 98)
      - Paris (Box 98)
      - Washington (Box 98)
    - ROUSSEAU, Jacques, 1630-1693 (Box 98)
    - ROUSSEAU, Theodore, 1812-1867 (Box 98–99)
      - Paris (Box 99)
    - ROY, Pierre, 1880- (Box 99)
    - ST. AUBIN, Augustin de, 1737-1807 (Box 99)
    - ST. AUBIN, Gabriel, 1724-1780 (Box 99)
    - SANTERRE, Jean-Baptiste, 1651-1717 (Box 99)
    - SCHEFFER, Ary, 1795-1858 (Box 99)
    - SERUSIER, Paul, 1864-1927 (Box 99)
    - SEURAT, Georges, 1859-1891 (Box 99)
      - Photographs (Box 99)
      - Drawings (Box 99)
      - Paintings (Box 99–100)
        - Buffalo (Box 100)
        - Chicago (Box 100)
        - London (Box 100)
        - New York (Box 100)
        - Otterlo (Box 100)
        - Paris (Box 100)
        - Philadelphia (Box 100)
        - Troyes (Box 100)
    - SIGNAC, Paul, 1863-1935 (Box 100)
    - SISLEY, Alfred, 1839-1899 (Box 100–101)
    - SOULAGES, Pierre, 1919- (Box 101)
    - SOUTINE, Chaim, 1893-1943 (Box 101)
    - STAEL, Nicolas de, 1914-1955 (Box 101)
    - STEINLEN, Alexandre, 1859-1923 (Box 101)
    - STELLA, Jacques (Box 101)
    - SUBLEYRAS, Pierre Hubert, 1699-1749 (Box 101)
    - TANGUY, Yves, 1900-1955 (Box 101)
    - TASSEL, Jean, 1608-1667 (Box 101)
    - TATTEGRAIN, Francois, 1852-1916 (Box 101)
    - TESTELIN, Louis, 1615-1655 (Box 101)
    - TISSOT, James, 1836-1902 (Box 101)
    - TOCQUE, Louis, 1696-1772 (Box 101)
    - TOULOUSE-LAUTREC, Henri de, 1864-1901 (Box 101)
      - Drawings (Box 101)
      - Paintings (Box 101–102)
        - Chicago (Box 102)
        - Cleveland (Box 102)
        - New York (Box 102)
        - Paris (Box 102)
    - TOURNIER, Jean-T., 1604-ca. 1670 (Box 102)
    - TROY, Francois de, ca. 1645-1730 (Box 102)
    - TROYON, Constant, 1810-1865 (Box 102)
    - UTRILLO, Maurice, 1883-1955 (Box 102)
      - Chicago (Box 102)
      - New York (Box 102)
      - Paris (Box 102)
    - VALENCIENNES, Pierre Henri de, 1750-1819 (Box 102)
    - VALENTIN de Boullogne, Jean, 1591-1634 (Box 102)
    - VALMIER, Georges, 1885- (Box 102)
    - VASARELY, Victor, 1906 or 1908-1997 (Box 102)
    - VERDIER, Francois, 1651-1730 (Box 102)
    - VERNET, Charles (Carle), 1789-1883 (Box 102)
    - VERNET, Claude-Joseph, 1714-1789 (Box 102)
    - VERNET, Horace, 1789-1863 (Box 102)
    - VIEN, Joseph Marie, 1716-1809 (Box 102)
    - VIERIA da Silva, M.E. (Box 102–103)
    - VIGEE-LEBRUN, Mme. Marie Louise Elizabeta, 1755-1842 (Box 103)
      - Paris (Box 103)
      - Versailles (Box 103)
    - VIGNON, Claude (Box 103)
    - VILLON, Jacques, 1875-1963 (Box 103)
      - Drawings (Box 103)
      - Paintings (Box 103)
        - New Haven (Box 103)
        - New York (Box 103)
        - Paris (Box 103)
    - VINCENT, Francois Andre (Box 103)
    - VITALIS, Marcari (Box 103)
    - VIVIN, Louis (Box 103)
    - VLAMINCK, Maurice de, 1876- (Box 103)
      - Chicago (Box 103)
      - New Haven (Box 103)
      - Paris (Box 103)
    - VOUET, Simon, 1590-1649 (Box 103)
      - Private Collection (Box 103–104)
      - Places (Box 104)
      - Brussels (Box 104)
      - London (Box 104)
      - Lyon (Box 104)
      - Nantes (Box 104)
      - Naples (Box 104)
      - New York (Box 104)
      - Paris (Box 104)
        - Louvre (Box 104)
      - Rome (Box 104)
      - Versailles (Box 104)
    - VUILLARD, Edouard, 1868-1940 (Box 105)
      - Private Collection (Box 105)
      - Places (Box 105)
      - New York (Box 105)
    - WARDQUIER, Henry de, 1881- (Box 105)
    - WATTEAU, Jean-Antoine, 1684-1721 (Box 105)
      - Drawings (Box 105)
        - London (Box 105)
        - New Haven (Box 105)
        - Paris (Box 105)
      - Paintings (Box 105)
        - Berlin (Box 105–106)
        - Dresden (Box 106)
        - Edinburgh (Box 106)
        - London (Box 106)
        - Nantes (Box 106)
        - New York (Box 106)
        - Paris (Box 106)
          - Louvre (Box 106)
            - Embarkation for Cythera (Box 106)
              - Gilles (Box 106)
            - Judgment of Paris (Box 106)
        - Valenciennes (Box 106)
        - Washington (Box 106)
    - WOOG, Raymond, 1875- (Box 106)
    - ZIEM, Felix, 1821-1911 (Box 106)
- Painting Germany (Box 106)
  - General (Box 106)
  - Artists Unknown (Box 106)
  - Romanesque (Box 106)
  - Gothic (Box 106)
  - 13th century (Box 106)
  - 14th century (Box 106)
    - Cologne Master (Box 106)
    - Master Bertram (Box 106)
      - Hamburg (Box 106)
        - Grabon Altar (Box 106)
      - Hanover (Box 106)
    - Master of the Honenfurther Passion Cycle (Box 106)
    - Master of the Klosterneuberg Altar (Box 106)
    - Master of S. Veronica (Box 106)
  - 15th century (Box 106)
    - Cologne School (Box 106)
    - Master of the Darmstadt Passion (Box 106)
    - Master Francke (Box 106)
    - Master of the Glorification of the Virgin (Box 106)
    - Master of the Golden Panel (Box 106)
    - Master of the Halepagen Altars (Box 106)
    - Master of the Hausbuch (Box 106)
    - Master of Heiligenkreuz (Box 106)
    - Master of the Imhoff Altarpiece, ca. 1420 (Box 106)
    - Master of the Life of Mary/ Life of the Virgin, fl. 1460-1480 (Box 106)
    - Master of the Middle Rhine (Box 106)
    - Master of Passion of Lyversberg (Box 107)
    - Master of S. Bartholomew (Box 108)
    - Master of S. Severin (Box 108)
    - Master of the Stersinger (Box 108)
    - Master of the Tegernsee Tabula Magna (Box 108)
    - Master of Tucher Altarpiece (Box 108)
    - Master of Werden (see Master of the Life of Mary) (Box 108)
    - Master of Wiederheim (Box 108)
    - Master of Wilten (Box 108)
  - 16th century (Box 108)
    - Master of Messkirch (Box 108)
    - Master of Pulkau (Box 108)
  - 17th century (Box 108)
  - 18th century, 19th century (Box 108)
  - Artists Known (Box 108)
    - AACHEN, Hans von, 1552-1615 (Box 108)
    - ACHENBACH, Andreas, 1815-1910 (Box 108)
    - ALDEGREVER, Heinrich, 1502-ca. 1561 (Box 108)
    - ALTDORFER, Albrecht, ca. 1480-1538 (Box 108)
      - Berlin (Box 108)
      - Chicago (Box 108)
      - Frankfurt (Box 108)
      - Munich (Box 108)
      - Vienna (Box 108)
    - AMBERGER, Christoph (Box 108)
    - BALDUNG, Hans, ca. 1484-1545 (Box 108)
      - Drawings (Box 108–109)
      - Paintings (Box 109)
        - Basel (Box 109)
        - Berlin (Box 109)
        - Budapest (Box 109)
        - Cassel (Box 109)
        - Cleveland (Box 109)
        - London (Box 109)
        - Nurnberg (Box 109)
        - Vienna (Box 109)
    - BECKMANN, Max, 1884-1950 (Box 109)
      - Berlin (Box 109)
      - Frankfurt (Box 109)
      - New York (Box 109)
    - BENDEMANN, Eduard J.F., 1811-1884 (Box 109)
    - BERGMAN, Michel Ella, 20th century (Box 109)
    - BERGMULLER, Johann Georg, 1688-1762 (Box 109)
    - BLECHEN, Karl, 1798-1840 (Box 109)
    - BOCKLIN, Arnold, 1827-1901 (Box 109)
    - BRUYN, Bartholomaus, 1493-1555 (Box 109)
    - BUCHHEISTER, Carl, 1890- (Box 109)
    - BURGKMAIR, Hans the Elder, 1473-1531 (Box 109)
    - CAMPENDONK, Heinrich, 1889-1957 (Box 109)
    - CORINTH, Lovis Joseph, 1858-1925 (Box 109)
    - CORNELIUS, Peter von, 1783-1867 (Box 109–110)
    - CRANACH, Lucas the Elder, 1472-1553 (Box 110)
      - Berlin (Box 110)
      - Brussels (Box 110)
      - Copenhagen (Box 110)
      - Dresden (Box 110)
      - Florence (Box 110)
      - Frankfurt (Box 110)
      - Hartford (Box 110)
      - Leipzig (Box 110)
      - Leningrad (Box 110)
      - Liverpool (Box 110)
      - London (Box 110)
      - New Haven (Box 110)
      - New York (Box 110)
      - Oslo (Box 110)
      - Paris (Box 110)
      - Philadelphia (Box 110)
      - Rome (Box 110)
      - Sarasota (Box 110)
      - Weimar (Box 110)
    - CRANACH, Lucas the Younger, 1515-1586 (Box 110)
    - DEFREGGER, Franz von, 1855-1921 (Box 110)
    - DIX, Otto, 1891-1969 (Box 110)
      - Berlin (Box 110)
      - Dresden (Box 110)
      - New York (Box 110)
    - DULBERG, Ewald (Box 110)
    - DURER, Albrecth, 1471-1528 (Box 110)
      - Drawings (Box 110)
        - Animals (Box 110)
        - Drapery Studies (Box 110)
        - Equestrian (Box 110)
        - Hands (Box 110)
        - Heads (Box 110–111)
        - Landscapes (Box 111)
        - Maximillian's Prayer Book (Box 111)
        - Mythology (Box 111)
        - Nudes (Box 111)
        - Plants/Trees (Box 111)
        - Portraits (Box 111)
        - Self-Portraits (Box 111)
        - Religious (Box 111)
          - Saints (Box 111)
          - Virgins and Holy Families (Box 111)
        - Secular (Box 111)
        - Theory and Measurement (Box 111)
      - Paintings (Box 112)
        - Berlin (Box 112)
        - Dresden (Box 112)
        - Florence (Box 112)
        - Lisbon (Box 112)
        - London (Box 112)
        - Lugano (Box 112)
        - Madrid (Box 112)
        - Munich (Box 112)
          - Alte Pinacoteka (Box 112)
        - New York (Box 112)
        - Nurnberg (Box 112)
        - Paris (Box 112)
        - Vienna (Box 112)
        - Vierhouten (Box 112)
        - Washington (Box 112)
    - EHRLER, Fritz, 20th century (Box 112)
    - ELSHEIMER, Adam, 1578-1610 (Box 112–113)
    - ENGERT, Erasmus, 1796-1871 (Box 113)
    - ERNST, Max, 1891-1976 (Box 113)
      - 1910-1929 (Box 113)
      - 1930-1976 (Box 113)
    - FELPACHER, Johann, fl. 1639-1678 (Box 113)
    - FEUERBACH, Anselm, 1829-1850 (Box 113)
    - FOHR, Carl Philipp, 1795-1818 (Box 113)
    - FRIEDRICH, Caspar David, 1774-1840 (Box 112–113)
      - Dresden (Box 113)
      - Leipzig (Box 113)
    - FRIES, Hans, 1465-1520 (Box 113)
    - FRUEAUF, Roland the Elder, ca. 1440-1507 (Box 113)
    - FRUEAUF, Roland the Younger, fl. 1503-1545 (Box 114)
    - FUHRICH, Joseph von, 1800-1885 (Box 114)
    - GARTNER, Eduard, 1801-1885 (Box 114)
    - GEBHARDT, Edouard von, 1838-1925 (Box 114)
    - GOETHE, Johann Wolfgang von, 1750-1832 (Box 114)
    - GRAF, Urs, ca. 1484-ca. 1527 (Box 114)
    - GRAFF, Anton, 1736-1813 (Box 114)
    - GRIEN, Hans Baldung, 1484-1545 (Box 114)
    - GROSZ, George, 1893-1959 (Box 114)
    - GRUNEWALD, Matthias, ca. 1480-1528 (Box 114)
      - Drawings (Box 114)
      - Paintings (Box 114)
        - Basel (Box 114)
        - Colmar (Box 114)
          - Unterlinden Museum (Box 114)
            - Isenheim Altarpiece (Box 114)
              - Exterior: S. Anthony, Crucifixion, S. Sebastian (Box 114)
              - Second Interior: SS. Anthony Paul, Sculptures, Temptation of S. Anthony (Box 114–115)
              - Predella (Box 115)
          - Munich (Box 115)
          - Stuppach (Box 115)
          - Washington (Box 115)
    - HANS von Aachen, 1552-1615 (Box 115)
    - HECKEL, Erich, 1883-1970 (Box 115)
    - HEEMSKERCK, Maerten van, 1498-1574 (Box 115)
    - HEINTZ, Josef the Younger, 1600-1678 (Box 115)
    - HERLIN, F., fl. 1459-1499 (Box 115)
    - HINTZE, Johann Heinrich, 1800-1862 (Box 115)
    - HINZ, Johann, 1662-1700 (Box 115)
    - HOERLE, Angelika (Box 115)
    - HOFER, Karl, 1878-1955 (Box 115)
    - HOLBEIN, Hans the Elder, ca. 1465-1524 (Box 115)
    - HOLBEIN, Hans the Younger, 1494-1543 (Box 115)
      - Drawings (Box 115)
        - London (Box 115)
        - Windsor (Box 115)
      - Paintings (Box 116)
        - Basel (Box 116)
        - Berlin (Box 116)
        - Dresden (Box 116)
        - Florence (Box 116)
        - Frankfurt-am-Main (Box 116)
        - Hague (Box 116)
        - Hannover (Box 116)
        - London (Box 116)
          - National Gallery (Box 116)
        - New York (Box 116)
          - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 116)
          - Frick Collection (Box 116)
        - Paris (Box 116)
        - Rome (Box 116)
        - Vienna (Box 116)
        - Washington (Box 116)
    - HUBER, Wolfgang, ca. 1485-1553 (Box 116)
    - HUMMEL, Johann Erdmann, 1769-1852 (Box 116)
    - ITTEN, Johannes, 1888-1967 (Box 116)
    - JAENISCH, Hans (Box 116)
    - JANLENSKY, Alexe, 1867- (Box 116)
    - KALKREUTH, Leopold von, 1855-1928 (Box 116)
    - KAULBACH, Wilhelm von, 1805-1874 (Box 116)
    - KERSTING, Friedrich, Georg (Box 116)
    - KESTING, Edmund, 1892-1970 (Box 116)
    - KIRCHNER, Ernst Ludwig, 1880-1938 (Box 116)
    - KLEIN, Johann Adam, 1792-1875 (Box 116)
    - KLINGER, Max, 1857-1920 (Box 116)
    - KOCH, Joseph Anton, 1768-1839 (Box 116)
    - KRUGER, Franz, 1797-1857 (Box 117)
    - KULMBACH, Hans von (Box 117)
    - LAIB, Konrad, fl. 1448-157 (Box 117)
    - LEIBL, Wilhelm, 1844-1900 (Box 117)
    - LENBACH, Franz von, 1836-1904 (Box 117)
    - LESSING, Karl Friedrich (Box 117)
    - LIEBERMANN, Max, 1847-1935 (Box 117)
    - LISS, Johann, 1597-1629 (Box 117)
    - LUCHNER, Stephan, fl. 1410-1451 (Box 117)
    - MACKE, August, 1887-1914 (Box 117)
    - MAIR, Johann Ulrich, 1630-1704 (Box 117)
    - MAIR von Landshut, fl. 1485-1510 (Box 117)
    - MANUEL (Box 117)
    - MARC, Franz, 1880-1916 (Box 117)
    - MAREES, 1837-1887 (Box 117)
    - Master of the Castle Lichtenstein, fl. 1430-1460 (Box 117)
    - MENGS, Anton Raphael, 1728-1779 (Box 117)
    - MENZEL, Adolf von, 1815-1905 (Box 118)
    - MIELICH, Hans, 1515-1573 (Box 118)
    - MIGNON, Abraham, 1640-1679 (Box 118)
    - MODERSOHN-BECKER, Paula, 1876-1907 (Box 118)
    - MOLZAHN, Johannes, 1892-1965 (Box 118)
    - MORGNER, Wilhelm, 1891-1917 (Box 118)
    - MOSER, Lucas, fl. 1431 (Box 118)
    - MUELLER, Otto (Box 118)